hello
Speaker 1 (higher-pitched voice): everyone i'm stephanie hamill welcome to in focus so the ceo of pfizer thinks that if you spread misinformation on covid19 vaccines you're a
Speaker 2: criminal and i'm not exaggerating he actually said this during an
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): interview watch there is a very
small part
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): of professionals which they circulate on purpose misinformation so that they will mislead those that they have concerns those people
are
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): They're
not bad
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): people, they're criminals because they literally
cost
Speaker 4: them millions of
lives.
Speaker 1 (higher-pitched voice): - Now, people definitely shouldn't be purposefully spreading misinformation about vaccines and COVID-19, but my question is, what's his definition of misinformation? That could literally mean anything. So if you have questions about the vaccine or take issues with the mandates, you could be a criminal, or at least in his eyes.
Speaker 1 (higher-pitched voice): please. Yeah, a lot of CEOs would love to criminize people who criticize their products. Also, take a look at this super creepy meme. Someone at Pfizer seriously thought this would be a good idea. It shows some goofy looking character gravitating towards wild conspiracies theories, while some weird looking pink blob
Speaker 1 (higher-pitched voice): tries to pull the character back. It's rather bizarre, isn't it? And this is on their official account. Go check it out yourself if you don't believe me. And to top things off, Pfizer blocked people from even leaving comments on this tweet. I wonder why. Meantime, the White House is telling businesses to proceed with the vaccine mandates despite a court-ordered pause. So do courts no longer matter? Last time I checked,
we still
Speaker 1 (higher-pitched voice): had a system of checks and balances. Join me now representing Kentucky's fourth district, Congressman Thomas Massey,
Speaker 1 (higher-pitched voice): Congressman, thank you so much for joining me. So, Congressman, first, I'll get your reaction to the CEO of Pfizer and his remarks about misinformation and that you could potentially be a criminal if you're spreading misinformation. And again, I'm not for people lying or making up crazy things about the vaccine, but I am a little skeptical about what he considers misinformation.
Well,
Speaker 5: you know, he's a veterinarian and I don't think a lot of people know that. So I find that interesting, but, you know, they're
Speaker 6: treating natural immunity like a conspiracy
Speaker 7: theory. Is that misinformation to say that your natural immunity, if you've already had COVID, is much better than the vaccine? We've got over a dozen studies that show that. Would that be misinformation? Would that make me a criminal for tweeting that?
Speaker 7: And, you know, that that meme or whatever it was that Pfizer put out there, that's very creepy. You know, I don't think they're allowed to advertise their drug. It's still experimental, at least the one that you can get
Speaker 8: in the United States. But they don't need to advertise because Congress gave CDC one billion dollars to promote this drug for them.
Speaker 8: And is it a conspiracy theory to say that the vaccine wears off or that it doesn't stop you from spreading it? Because we know that it does. It doesn't stop you from spreading it. There are studies that show the vaccinated are giving the virus to the vaccinated. Which of those are conspiracy theories? I would love to know what he's talking about.
Speaker 9: Yeah, exactly. And I'm glad that you pointed all that stuff out. So, yeah, I mean, if you're vaccinated, you can still spread COVID-19. You can
Speaker 1 (higher-pitched voice): still get COVID-19. And so I have a feeling that's where they're going with this. They don't want people to talk about that. And again, not an anti-vaxxer. I just want people to have the ability to choose what's best for their bodies. They should talk to their doctor. And so I'm really bothered by this government mandate. Obviously, I'm totally disturbed by
this.
Speaker 1 (higher-pitched voice): the fact that Biden thinks he's above the courts. This is tyranny. This is what a dictator acts like. Yes,
it's
Speaker 6: violence. Biden is committing violence on the American people. He doesn't have the authority to do this. If you
Speaker 7: believe a president can mandate a medical treatment for every American as a condition of their employment, then you're morally bankrupt and constitutionally illiterate. And the courts are, I mean, as I predicted, and a lot of other people predicted this, They're gonna shoot this mandate
Speaker 7: down. It's a bully's bluff. You know, Biden,
if he
Speaker 7: really wanted to put this in the law, he would have brought it to Congress and had us vote on it. But it's really just a bluff. And, you know, he's telling people to go ahead, even though the court has called his bluff, he's telling companies to go ahead and implement this. We've got three deadlines coming up. We've got the January 4th deadline for his unconstitutional OSHA mandate. We've got the December 8th deadline for the federal contractors, and we got the November 22nd
Speaker 7: deadline for federal employees. Every person from the administration that I get in front of me in a hearing, I ask them, how many medical exemptions or religious exemptions have you granted within your department? I asked Merrick Garland that. He acknowledged that legally he has to, but then he admitted
that he
Speaker 7: didn't know if he had granted a single exemption to DOJ employees, even though the law requires that.
Speaker 9: yeah and then congressman if the vaccine is so good why are they demonizing people who might have some questions or want to wait i mean i found that meme to be again very weird and almost offensive too so rather than explaining to people you know the vaccine is good and it's going to offer this type of protection and you should consider it
Speaker 9: It's like they're mocking people that are waiting for whatever reason it might be, whether it be religious
Speaker 1 (higher-pitched voice): or a health reason, or maybe they just want to wait it out, or they've already been diagnosed with COVID-19 recovered. And as you pointed
Speaker 9: out, antibodies, they
work.
Speaker 10: Right. I'm not an anti-vaxxer, by the way, but I am anti-vax mandate. By the way, is
Speaker 7: it a conspiracy theory to say that the former FDA director is now on the board of Pfizer monetizing his connections over there? Is it a conspiracy theory to point out that the CDC changed their own definition of vaccination just days before Biden announced his vaccine mandate because they realized and we've got these from FOIA requests in their emails, they realized that
Speaker 11: their own definition of vaccination.
Speaker 11: didn't meet the COVID shots. And
Speaker 12: then, as you know, I'm sure you've seen the hard push on getting kids vaccinated
Speaker 9: ages 5 through 11. And now they've rolled out Big Bird as part of the campaign. We have the video roll tape. Something's
Speaker 13 (higher-pitched voice): going on down at the store. I wonder what's... It's kind of funny. I mean, it's strange. I mean, there's... Well, there's all kinds of people, and they're all in a line, and they don't look like they're buying candy. And there's a sign that says...
Speaker 13 (higher-pitched voice): don't wait vaccinate so
i will
Speaker 9: say i love what uh governor ron de santis in florida is doing when it comes to the vaccines for kids he's like i'm gonna leave that up to the parents and their doctors and they can all figure it out i'm definitely not going to force this on kids
Speaker 14: Yeah, I mean, if Big Bird wants to take the shot, Big Bird can take the shot. Exactly.
Speaker 7: But nobody should mandate this vaccine for people or imaginary animals. And, you know, it's kind of creepy the way they're pushing this on children. Again, they can't advertise it. They can't legally advertise it. So they're using all these other methods to push it on children. And I just think it's creepy.
Speaker 7: There's elevated chances of myocarditis for people under the age of 24 as compared to older people, yet there's less risk from COVID and therefore less benefit from the vaccine for the younger folks. It's a risk versus reward. Every parent needs to balance this because if the child does suffer from some rare
Speaker 15: adverse effect, it's going to be the parent who has to take care of that child.
Speaker 9: - Yeah, exactly, there's no help for parents there. And we did interview a parent on this show whose daughter did have a rare side effect from the vaccine during the trials. And she says, basically Pfizer, no one wants to talk to her, no one cares, and her daughter's really suffering. And it's really tragic. I mean, it was a really hard interview to get through. I was like crying
Speaker 16: during the interview. Now, I wanted to ask you this. Do you guys still have the mask rules on the floor of the house?
We do,
Speaker 17: but there's some of us who refuse to wear the mask. Marjorie Taylor Greene, Ralph Norman and I
Speaker 6: have a lawsuit in federal court against Nancy Pelosi because she's automatically taking it out of our paychecks. And Marjorie's racked up a lot bigger fine than I have. I kind of sneak on the floor and vote and sneak out. I think our founding fathers would be ashamed of what's going on on the floor of the House of Representatives. Yet
i
Speaker 6: think i know
Speaker 18: where you're going with this nancy pelosi what do you know about nancy pelosi when she's not on the floor yeah
Speaker 19 (higher-pitched voice): she was she was caught at a billionaire's wedding in the middle of a crowd with no mask on but i also wanted to point this out too i don't know if you saw this video it's pretty ridiculous it's of senator chuck schumer like partying it up in puerto rico with no mask on and we have the video i must warn people it's very cringe so if you feel like you can't handle the
cringe
Speaker 19 (higher-pitched voice): Look away. Roll
Speaker 20: tape. Yucky.
Speaker 21: Anyway,
so he has no
Speaker 19 (higher-pitched voice): mask on. He's partying it up. So we have House Speaker Nancy Pelosi and Senator Schumer. They're all for, like, everyone wearing a mask at the state at the United States
Speaker 12: Capitol. Yet, like, when they're out having fun, no one wears masks. like it doesn't make any
sense
Speaker 12: to me
i'll
Speaker 6: agree that was very cringy they are big they're the biggest hypocrites on the planet i mean you should not follow what they say you should look at what they
Speaker 7: are doing and you know interestingly chuck schumer was the author of the 1993 religious freedom restoration act which requires requires the government to make exemptions religious accommodations for
Speaker 7: for people who apply for them, yet none of those are being
Speaker 6: granted within the military or within the federal government or with federal contractors. As far as I can tell, they're breaking the law.
-
Speaker 19 (higher-pitched voice): Yeah, I'm wondering, do you guys get double the fines if you wear, let's go Brandon, masks on the floor? 'Cause I know that people were pretty upset about the one congressman who wore that. I mean, that made like national headline.
Speaker 19 (higher-pitched voice): -
Speaker 22: Well, Lauren Boebert has a dress that says, "Let's go Brandon" on the back of it. It's
Speaker 7: red and white. I hope she wears that on the floor. Some of us have worn messes, say, "Let's go Brandon." And I think the state of Virginia almost changed their state motto to
Speaker 23: "Let's go Brandon" last Tuesday.
- Yeah, I
Speaker 9: mean, basically it should be that. You know, again, just back to the mandates and how Biden thinks he's above the courts and our judicial system.
You know, it
Speaker 9: seems like people don't want to follow certain rules, but they want us to follow the rules. And if you just look at like the border crisis, for example, so, you know, they're not following the laws and so they expect us to follow the laws and just listen to them. And the big thing here is it's a slippery slope. So people cave to this one because they're like, you know, I want the vaccine and it's fine and I'm OK with this. But I warn people that, again, you give the government this much power, nothing will stop them in the future.
Speaker 6: That's right. If you believe that this president has the power to mandate a drug, that everybody in this country take a drug, that's almost cult-like. That is not the way this country was founded. The courts have struck it down. He's telling people to ignore the courts. He's basically telling people to be lawless. And, you know, I've co-sponsored a bill. I
Speaker 7: think it's Andy Biggs is the author to eliminate OSHA completely, because those people who are at OSHA, I mean, they are following orders. That's true. But they know what they're doing is
Speaker 6: illegal and unconstitutional. Well,
Speaker 24: Congressman, we appreciate your insight and fighting the good fight. Thank you so much for joining
us on
Speaker 24: the show. Thanks
for having me
Speaker 25: on, Stephanie. Of
Speaker 24: course.